

# RAUL PAYA

### Software Developer

### **PROFILE**

I'm a former electromechanical engineer at Spanish Navy. I had been on duty for more than 10 years.

After early retirement, I'm trying to refocus and pursue my professional career as a software developer, one of my biggest passions.

I came to Japan in 2017 to study programming with the objective to land a job here and establish myself in this country.

Now I'm based in Tokyo and looking for a full-time job in the software development industry.

Even though my experience as a programmer is not solid yet, I have gained lot of hand-on experience in many other areas like as a team leader, resource management and knowledge of IT industry in general.

I see myself a highly responsible and confident person at work, and I'm always studying new matters on my spare time.

For personal hobbies, I like running and cycling to keep me healthy. Should you have any concern or question about my profile and capabilities, please feel free to contact me.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: 070-4471-0132 WEBSITE: https://raulet.dev/ EMAIL: contact@raulet.dev

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Gokuraku - Spanish Cybercafe

1999 - 2007

Computer technician in a Cybercafe.

### Spanish Navy

2007 - 2017

Busines Administration(6 years), Electromechanical Engineering (4 years).

## **EDUCATION**

#### EE. Antonio de Escaño

2011-2013

Electromechanical Engineering in a Vocational School.

### Intercultural Japanese Language School

2017-2019

Japanese language.

### Yamanashi Information Systems

2019-2021

Software Developing in a Vocational School

### Certificates:

• C/C++

Java.

Jw-CAD.

JLPT N3.

**Photoshop** 

## **SKILLS**

Linux

| Spanish | English | Japanese     |
|---------|---------|--------------|
| Unity   | C/C++   | C#           |
| Java    | Lua     | Visual Basic |
| HTML    | css     | JavaScript   |
| PHP     | NodeJS  | React Native |
| MySQL   | MongoDB | Access       |
| Excel   | Jw-CAD  | Git / Github |
|         |         |              |

Maya